I'm Hachi.
我叫八公
This is about a love story between my girlfriend and I.
这是我和我女友的爱情故事
She is a bit different, but super cool.
她有点与众不同 但她非常酷
She wields a sword.
她的武器是一把剑
She's unbelievably strong.
她强壮得不可思议
When I met her, I learned the joy and sadness of being in love,
遇见她之后 我才了解了 陷入爱河的快乐与悲伤
and what it means to truly love someone.
以及 真正爱上某人意味着什么
In any case, I learned what "love" is.
总的来说 我学到了“爱”为何物
She really is my special person.
她真的是我生命中最特别的人
It might be misleading to say "person,"
用“人”形容她有点不恰当
Since my girlfriend
因为我的女友
is a Yokai who was bound a long time ago.
是很久以前被困住的一只妖怪
My Yokai girlfriend crossed a tremendous amount of time
我的妖怪女友跨越了漫漫时间长河
to arrive in the present day,
来到现代
with a huge secret.
随她而来的 还有一个天大的秘密
I had no idea about her secret back then.
那时我还对她的秘密一无所知
This is a love story between me and my dear, and slightly scary,
这是我和我亲爱的、有点可怕的
Yokai girlfriend.
妖怪女友的爱情故事
It all started with a strange incident.
这一切始于一件怪事
ONE WEEK AGO
一周前
Love?
爱？
POST IN STORY
发布快拍
UPLOAD COMPLETE
已完成上传
I just want to free her!
我只是想还她自由！
You fool!
你这蠢货！
That isn't love.
那不是爱
That's a story of betrayal.
这是一个关于背叛的故事
It's coming! I'll go forward.
来了！我去前面
We can do it. Yes! They're coming.
我们能做到的 太棒了！他们来了
You can do it. Yes!
你可以的 很好！
Hikari, help me out.
小光 帮我一把
-Okay. -Give me one.
-好 -给我一个
-Okay, nice! -Oh...
-很好 漂亮！ -噢…
MAI SENT A STAMP
麻衣：发送了一个表情
Morning Mai! I'm off now!
早上好 麻衣！我出发喽！
PEEK
偷瞄
Hachi, the flank.
八公 注意侧翼
I can't give you death.
我无法赐予你死亡
-Hachi. -Hachi, the flank!
-八公 -八公 侧翼防御！
What's up? Hachi, the flank!
你干什么呢？八公 侧翼！
How are you, Mai?
你怎么样 麻衣？
-Hachi, the flank! -Where did you go?
-八公 侧翼防御！ -你跑哪去了？
The flank!
注意侧翼！
Battle test complete.
战斗测试完成
The Opposing team completed the mission.
敌方队伍完成了任务
You lost.
你方战败
I repeat. You lost.
我重复一遍 你方战败
What were you doing? We were about to level up.
你刚才在干什么？ 我们马上就要升级了
I'm sorry. I got a message.
抱歉 我收到一条信息
Turn your phone off! That's the most basic rule.
把你的手机关机！这是最基本的规矩
It was from my girlfriend.
是我女友发来的
Nothing is more important than gaining levels.
没有比升级更重要的事
-There is. -Totally.
-有的 -有很多
Wait. What girlfriend?
等等 什么女友？
Your response is slow.
你的反应真够慢的
What girlfriend?
哪来的女友？
I met her on a fanzine site.
我和她是在粉丝杂志网站上认识的
We get along well, and everything about her is very cute.
我们相处得很融洽 她的一切都很可爱
I mean, I haven't met her in person yet.
我是说 我和她还没见过面
A gamer is having an online romance? How typical.
电竞选手网恋？好俗套的剧情
Because of people like you,
就是因为你这种人
people think gamers are lame and asocial.
大家才会觉得电竞选手 既无趣还不会社交
Get it together.
打起精神吧
You always do that when you get nervous. Stop, Wetty.
你一紧张就会这么做 别擦了 “汗仔”
Don't call me that.
别这么叫我
He's right. Abuse of power.
他说得对 你这是滥用职权
I'm just passionate about games. Right, Hikari?
我只是非常热爱游戏 对吧 小光？
Thanks to all you HikaristsI I'm so happy. I love you all!
谢谢各位光迷！ 我太开心了 爱你们！
Don't forget to follow me. Hikari out.
别忘了关注我 小光下播喽
Well, if you ask me,
这个嘛 要我说
gamers equal nerds with money,
电竞选手除了有钱的书呆子
and the rest are harmless losers.
就是无害的废柴
I'm not a loser.
我不是废柴
You're more like a loyal dog, Hachi, rather than a loser.
你比废柴更糟 你更像是一只忠诚的狗 八公
-All right, let's do it again. -Yes.
-行了 我们再来一局 -好
Benitaro is a musclehead, so don't let it get to you.
贝尼塔罗就是个头脑简单的混蛋 别让他的话影响到你
By the way, are online girlfriends lame?
话说 搞网恋真的很差劲吗？
Your soft, tofu-like mentality worrying about that is lame.
差劲的是你的玻璃心 竟然为这种事烦心
Then there's nothing I can do!
我还能怎么办！
I have no confidence in myself.
我对自己毫无自信
I'll never be the main character no matter what I do.
不管我怎么努力 我永远无法成为故事中的主角
I'm just a nobody with no level-unlocking capabilities.
我只是压根无法升级的无名小卒
I sound like a total loser talking about this, too.
说这种话显得 我更像无可救药的废柴了
Why is everything so difficult?
为什么一切都那么难？
It's simple.
其实很简单
Games and love are the same. You just take on the next level.
游戏和爱是一样的 你只需升到下一级就好了
All you do is summon your girlfriend into the real world.
现在你只需把你的女朋友 召唤到现实世界中
Ask her out on a real date.
邀请她和你约会一次
What?
什么？
That's... What?
那…那算什么？
Here we go!
我要拍了！
-Hi. -Hi, Tadashi.
-嗨 -嗨 忠士
Mom, focus! This is my profile picture. Take it seriously.
妈 你专心点！你拍的是我的头像照 不要敷衍了事
Okay, step back one step.
好 你退后一步
Hachi!
八公！
I'll kill you if you drink my smoothie.
你敢喝我的冰沙 我就宰了你
Understood.
懂
Here we go!
我要拍喽！
-What? -I posted it.
-怎么了？ -我把它发布了
MAI I'm sorry about earlier
麻衣：之前的事我很抱歉
SENT A STAMP
麻衣：发送了一个表情
No problem! I had a lot bothering me today
没关系！我今天遇到了很多烦心事
How about you, Mai?
你过得怎么样 麻衣？
Me too!
我也是！
Misaki kept on making mean comments again today
今天美咲又一直嘲讽我
Mai, you're the only one I can talk to about everything
麻衣 只有你 能让我敞开心扉 畅聊一切
I feel the same way. I really like you, Hachi
你对我来说也是一样 我真的很喜欢你 八公
BLUSH
脸红
Okay.
就这么办
How about we go out to eat this weekend?
我们这个周末一起去吃顿饭怎么样？
I won't say anything mean to you.
我绝对不会嘲讽你
I'm sorry... I have plans already
抱歉…我已经有安排了
Why? I'm serious about you, Mai.
为什么？我对你是认真的 麻衣
I bought everything on your Amazon Wish List too
你亚马逊愿望清单里的所有东西 我都给你买了
I sent it.
我发出去了
VIDEO CALL
视频通话
CALLING
呼叫中
Who was that?
刚才那是谁？
Mai?
麻衣？
Mythology wasn't just handed down for entertainment purposes.
神话流传至今不仅仅是为了娱乐
There are unimaginable stories hidden behind it.
它们的背后藏着 无数令人无法想象的故事
That's all for today. We'll pick this up next week.
今天的课到此结束 我们下周再继续这个话题
I bet that was Mai's father.
那肯定是麻衣的父亲
Hachi, just forget it.
八公 别再纠结这事了
See her profile picture? It's authentic.
看到她的头像了吗？那么真实
Editing apps these days are impressive.
如今的修图软件都很厉害的
Hey, Wetty!
嘿 汗仔！
I heard you got scammed on a dating app.
我听说你在约会软件上被骗了
How did you find that out?
你怎么知道的？
Let's see...
我瞧瞧…
"We may be physically apart,
“虽然我们相隔万里
"but I've never been so close to anyone in my whole entire life."
“但我这一生中 从未感觉和其他人如此亲近”
Man, that's sick to say to a dude!
天啊 对男人说这种话真恶心！
Give it back.
把手机还给我
Inukai.
犬饲
Do you have a moment?
你有时间吗？
What?
什么事？
Thank you, Arisa.
亚里沙 谢谢你
-That'll be enough for today. -Yes.
-今天做到这里就行了 -好
Excuse me.
失陪了
Inukai, are you okay?
犬饲 你还好吗？
Yes, Masato has been that way since high school.
还好 正人从高中开始就是这样
There's something I'm worried about...
有件事让我很担心…
I'm worried, too!
我也很担心！
Everyone thinks I'm a loser. They call me "Wetty."
大家都觉得我是废柴 叫我“汗仔”
-This isn't an American teen drama. -"Wetty?"
-这又不是什么美国青少年狗血剧 -“汗仔”？
When I was talking to a girl in elementary school,
上小学的时候 每次我和女孩说话
I started to sweat a lot.
我都会出很多汗
When I told that story to the e-sports team,
有次我跟电竞队的人说了这个故事
the entire campus knew it the next day.
隔天就传遍了整个学校
Sweating is part of social awkwardness, which means I get nervous.
出汗是社交尴尬的一种表现 这代表我容易紧张
I know I have to do something about it...
我知道我必须想办法改善这个问题…
That must be hard,
想必那一定很辛苦
but I'm worried about something else.
但我担心的不是这件事
What?
诶？
It's about a student named Kouki Shikazono.
我担心的是一个叫鹿苑科希的学生
I haven't been able to get ahold of him for a week.
我已经和他失联整整一周了
Do you know anything about it, Inukai?
你对此有什么头绪吗 犬饲？
Um... I don't know.
这个嘛…我不清楚
Just like you, he was a different kind of a nerd,
他和你一样 是有点另类的书呆子
so I thought you might know something.
所以我以为你可能知道些什么
MUKURO POLICE DEPARTMENT
六畔警察署
Captain!
队长！
That blood found at the Keiho University library
在庆丰大学图书馆发现的血迹
matched the DNA of that missing Kouki Shikazono.
与失踪学生鹿苑科希的DNA相符
Now it gets super interesting.
接下来的事就非常有意思
No one hardly ever steps in to that old library's basement.
几乎从没人踏进过 那个旧图书馆的地下室
You need to request entry, however!
进入需要申请 然而！
There's no record of Kouki Shikazono's entry.
学校没有鹿苑科希的进出记录
It looks like he snuck in there.
看起来他是偷偷溜进去的
It's like he's to blame...
好像是他自作自受了…
It gets more interesting.
更加有意思的是
This book was found there.
这本书是在地下室找到的
Isn't this cut amazing?
这个切痕很神奇 对吧？
It's impossible to do this with a CNC laser cutter.
就算用数控激光切割机 也切不出这样利落的切面
Did the culprit use an iron-cutting sword? Or the user of Destructo Disc?
犯人用的是削铁如泥的剑吗？ 还是会用气圆斩的人？
Does that mean Krillin is the suspect?
这是不是意味着 嫌疑人是《龙珠》里的克林？
By the way, who are you?
先问一下 你是哪位？
Sir! I'm Nico Suzuki, and I've been assigned to First Investigation Division.
长官！我叫铃木妮可 刚被调至第一刑侦科
It's seriously awesome that the best captain here is my mentor!
我的导师竟然是这里最棒的队长 这真是太好了
I'm thrilled!
我超级激动！
-Suzuki. -Sir!
-铃木 -我在！
Get the report together.
去整理一份报告
Sir!
明白！
Kouki Shikazono?
鹿苑科希？
The one who went missing?
就是失踪的那个人？
Right! He was an occult fanatic.
没错！他是超自然事物的狂热爱好者
He was a little different.
但他跟别人还有点不一样
Take a look at this.
你看这个
It's a screenshot of a Story
这是一个“快拍”的截图
Kouki Shikazono posted before he went missing.
就是鹿苑科希失踪前发布的快拍
What do you think this is?
你看这像什么？
Ancient characters?
古代人物？
You sure are good, Hachi! I only understand bits and pieces of it,
不愧是八公！我只能看懂一点点
but I'm thinking it's a spell for some ritual.
但我觉得这是某种仪式的咒语
"Amanoenoma?"
“阿玛诺艾诺玛”？
"For those who seek love."
“给寻求爱情之人”
It looks like a spell to grant love.
看起来是求爱的咒语
Look at this.
你看这个
Isn't she cute? She looks like Mai!
她是不是很可爱？长得和麻衣很像！
I went too far.
我玩笑开过头了
I'm sorry.
对不起啦
A love spell...
爱情咒语…
Oh, man! If only I had a real girlfriend!
烦死了！ 如果我有一个真人女朋友就好了！
Then no one would harass me.
这样就没人来骚扰我了
Why don't you try the spell? You might get your wish.
不如你试试这个咒语？ 说不定能如愿以偿呢
No way!
不可能啦！
Airdrop it to me anyway.
不过 还是把图片 用Airdrop发给我吧
"To unleash the beast of desire,
“为释放欲望之兽
"collect the sacred devices."
“必须收集几样圣器”
An object to reflect your vanity.
一样能体现你虚荣心的物品
An object that broadcasts humanity's deceitful laws.
一样能将人类满是谎言的法律 广而告之的物品
The blood of a young virgin maiden.
年轻处女的血
Pervert!
变态！
I think a virgin boy's blood will do.
应该可以用处男的血充数吧
This is stupid.
这太傻了
Hey!
嘿！
Did that spell work?
是那个咒语起效了吗？
Jeez! I've been looking for you all morning.
真是的！我找了你一早上
I might have been looking for you, too.
也许我也一直在找你
What? Who are you? Creep!
什么？你谁啊？真恶心！
Of course not.
当然不可能起效了
I found you.
找到你了
What?
诶？
I'm Princess Izuna-imiki.
我是伊豆之内干姬公主
You must be Tadashi Inukai.
你一定是犬饲忠士吧
I've been looking for you.
我一直在找你
Me?
我？
Now, let's have intercourse.
现在 我们来做爱吧
Intercourse?
做爱？
Where's the camera? Isn't this one of Masato's pranks?
摄像机在哪儿？ 肯定是正人又搞恶作剧吧？
I'll go now.
我要走了
Where are you going?
你要去哪儿？
Tadashi Inukai.
犬饲忠士
I'm going to have intercourse with you right now.
我要和你做爱 现在就要
I'm sorry. Excuse me!
抱歉 先失陪了！
What was that?
刚才那是怎么回事？
Was I hallucinating? Have I gone mad?
是我出现幻觉了吗？我这是疯了吗？
Is this your residence?
这是你的住处吗？
What? When? Did you follow me? Why?
诶？你什么时候来的？ 你跟踪我？为什么？
We are going to have intercourse.
因为我们要做爱
That hurt!
好疼！
And her breath is cold.
她的呼吸是冰凉的
What?
干什么？
Wait one second!
慢着！
Are you halting the ritual?
你要暂停仪式吗？
This is new to me, too.
我也是第一次做这种事
Don't worry. It's just formality.
别担心 只是走个形式而已
But this is very special.
但这是很特别的事
Special?
特别？
Right. I think it should be special.
没错 我觉得这应该是特别的
It shouldn't be done on a whim like this.
不该一时兴起就这么做了
I mean I want to do it.
我是说 我想做
I want it to be special.
但我希望初夜是特别的
Enough with your nonsense.
你的废话说够了吧
-Hey! -Tadashi?
-喂！ -忠士？
Are you home?
你在家吗？
This is horrible. Move!
糟了 快让开！
Put your clothes on! Hurry! Your clothes!
把衣服穿上！快点！衣服穿上！
-Tadashi? -Wait!
-忠士？ -等一下！
Hi.
嗨
This isn't...
这不是…
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Here's your laundry. Make sure to put it away. There!
这是你洗好的衣服 把衣服收好 我走了！
How else do I explain it?
你还要我怎么解释？
A connection between the fact that you almost did it
你差点破处了的事实
and the fact you used that love spell?
和你用了那个爱情咒语之间有联系？
Whatever it is, I envy you.
不管怎样 我好羡慕你
Can you be serious here?
你严肃一点行不行？
Maybe I'll give it a try, too.
也许我也该试一次
-I swear I'll do this. -No! You'll ignore me for a whole week?
-你再这样 我发誓我会这么做 -不会吧！你要无视我整整一周？
Suddenly, a girl who wants to have intercourse with me shows up.
突然间 出现了一个 想和我做爱的女孩
You know it's some kind of a scam.
这肯定是某种骗局
I thought so, too!
一开始我也这么以为！
But she looked like she was really summoned by the spell.
但是她的样子看上去 像是真的被咒语召唤来的
Everything is different about her.
她的一切都是那么与众不同
It's as if she came from a different time period.
就仿佛她是从另一个时代穿越来的
By the way, what does she look like?
顺便一问 她长什么样？
She's slender.
她的身材修长
She's fair and has black hair.
皮肤白皙 披着一头黑发
Is she dressed like a female ninja with black armor and lots of weapons?
她是不是一副女忍者的装扮 身披黑色盔甲 还携带了很多武器？
Yes! How did you know that?
没错！你怎么知道？
Here you go.
请用
So you followed me after all?
你果然在跟踪我吧？
What is this mud water?
这泥水是什么东西？
It's cola.
是可乐
Why is this mud water mad?
这个泥水为什么疯了？
You never had it before? It's good.
你从来没喝过吗？很好喝的
I feel a burst of energy now.
我感受到一股能量喷薄而出
Okay! Let's have intercourse.
好了！我们来做爱吧
Keep it down.
小声点
But why me?
不过 你为什么选我？
Were you summoned by that spell?
你是被咒语召唤过来的吧？
You broke the seal and brought me back to this world.
你打破封印 把我带到了这个世界
If I don't have intercourse with a human by the hour of the ox,
如果我不在丑时前和某个人类做爱
I'll disappear from this world.
我就会从这个世上消失
-The hour of the ox? -No time can be wasted.
-丑时？ -这件事刻不容缓
Hold on a second! Izunaimi... What was it again?
等一下！伊豆之内…你叫什么来着？
That's long. Can I call you "Izzy?"
全名太长了 我可以叫你“伊姬”吗？
Go ahead.
没问题
Thanks. People call me "Hachi."
多谢 大家都叫我“八公”
It's actually Tadashi, but I got it after Hachi, the loyal dog.
我其实叫忠士 这个昵称 来自电影里那条叫八公的忠犬
Izzy, you're very attractive.
伊姬 你很有魅力
I'm interested in lots of things.
我想跟你一起做很多事
But to have intercourse, you know...
但是做爱嘛…
I think things should be done in steps.
我觉得我们应该一步一步来
So first, why don't we go on a date?
所以 我们先约个会怎么样？
A date?
约会？
We go out together and talk about ourselves...
就是我们一起出去玩 聊聊彼此的事…
I mean, I don't know...
我是说…
I've never been on a date.
我从没约过会
If we go on this "date" thing, then can we have intercourse?
等我们做完了你所谓的“约会” 就可以做爱了？
Well...
这个嘛…
If things go well.
如果一切顺利的话
Hachi, let's go.
八公 我们走吧
What? Wait!
什么？等等！
What?
搞什么？
Seriously?
不会吧？
Would you like one?
您要来一个吗？
Izzy, do you have any siblings?
伊姬 你有兄弟姐妹吗？
I have two older sisters.
我有两个姐姐
Where are you from?
你是哪里人？
Our family line goes back to Buzen during the Yayoi period.
我的家族起源于弥生时代的丰前国
I grew up on Kutsujima Island.
我从小在沓岛长大
Why do you ask?
你问这个做什么？
That's the whole point of a date.
这就是约会的意义啊
We get to know one another.
让我们了解彼此
Is knowing one another necessary to do an intercourse ritual?
了解彼此是做爱仪式的必要步骤吗？
I think it is.
我觉得是
Do this.
你做这个手势
Here. Look here, okay?
看这里 好吗？
It's to remember our first date.
这是我们第一次约会的纪念
Look who's here! It's Wetty!
瞧瞧这是谁啊！是汗仔！
Is she your girlfriend?
她是你的女朋友吗？
Well, she's not quite my girlfriend yet.
她现在还不是我的女朋友呢
Right! You can't be this lowly nobody's girlfriend!
也对！你可不能当 这种无名鼠辈的女友
Lowly nobody?
无名鼠辈？
-Someone that's insignificant. -Let's go.
-也就是没人在乎的小角色 -我们走吧
You look wild and gorgeous.
你看起来狂野又美丽
Why don't you dump him and come to a party?
不如你甩了他 来参加派对怎么样？
It's happening at my cousin Hayato's penthouse tonight.
派对今晚在我表兄弟 隼人的豪华顶层公寓举行
We won't go to Ippongi's party.
我们就不去参加一本木的派对了
I'm not inviting you.
我没有邀请你
Here.
你瞧
I'll see you there.
到时我们在那儿见
See you!
回见！
I bet Ippongi's party is full of rich arrogant people with no taste.
我敢说一本木的派对上 充满了没品又傲慢的富家子弟
They're all investors and frauds. They're all scum!
那些人就是一群投资诈骗犯 全是人渣！
Ippongi...
一本木…
Hachi, let's have intercourse right now!
八公 我们现在就做爱吧！
We just met, we have things to prepare, and my mother is home.
我们才刚认识 还要准备很多东西 而且我妈妈也在家
We should get to know each other.
我们还是先好好了解对方吧
Enough. If you won't do it, than I'll just look for a temporary mate.
够了 如果你不愿意 我就去找一个临时伴侣
I got my eyes on one.
我已瞄到了一个合适人选
I'm going to Ippongi's residence.
我要去一本木的住处
I will have intercourse there.
我去那里做爱就行了
What? Wait!
什么？等等！
Where is everyone?
大家都去哪了？
They all went to Ippongi's party. Where is she?
他们都去参加一本木的派对了 那女孩去哪了？
Izzy went to that party, too. Masato invited her.
伊姬也去那个派对了 正人邀请了她
Parties are stupid.
派对这种东西太蠢了
They'll have hangovers and puke.
等待他们的是宿醉和呕吐
It just ruins their record.
这会影响他们的竞技水平
I don't envy them at all. Let's go to an all-you-can-eat barbecue!
我完全不羡慕那些人 我们去吃烤肉自助吧！
Let's have salty ox tongue, then short ribs!
先吃咸牛舌 再吃排骨！
I'm going to Ippongi's party.
我要去参加一本木的派对
But you aren't invited.
可是没人邀请你啊
I followed Hayato's account. I know where it is.
我关注了隼人的社交账号 我知道派对地点在哪
Don't.
别去
Offal, then short ribs again!
先吃内脏 再吃排骨！
Just forget her.
你就忘掉那姑娘吧
You know you'll be in trouble if you don't quit now.
如果你不尽早放弃 你一定会麻烦缠身的
That missing Kouki Shikazono
失踪的鹿苑科希
disappeared after he posted that spell.
在发布了那条咒语后就人间蒸发了
Take a look at this.
你看这个
Doesn't she look like her?
那姑娘很像画上这个人 不是吗？
She's definitely dangerous.
她绝对是个危险人物
-She doesn't look like her. -Hachi.
-她们一点都不像 -八公
She likes me!
她喜欢我！
Someone actually likes me.
好不容易有一个真的喜欢我的人
This is an opportunity of a lifetime for me!
这对我来说 是一生只有一次的机会！
Give it up for Hayato!
让我们为隼人献上热烈的掌声！
There are two kinds of people.
这世上有两种人
A small fraction of successful winners
只有一小部分是成功的人生赢家
or the rest, the losers!
而剩下的 全是输家！
Which makes me...
这意味着我是…
A winner!
人生赢家！
That's right! A rich and distinguished family.
没错！出身于富裕而显赫的家庭
Ippongi's only son. Special by birth.
一本木家的独子 生来便与众不同
Furthermore, I was gifted with two things.
此外 我还被赐予了两件礼物
I don't know who you are,
虽然我并不认识你
but thank you, Satoshi Nakamoto,
但比特币的开发者 中本聪
the developer of Bitcoin!
谢谢你！
"Since the ancient times, the demon fox haunted a human male
“古时 妖狐会缠上一位人类男子
"and used that man as a host,
“将此人当做宿主
"and by having intercourse with that host,
“与宿主进行性交后
"it is able to regain its original powers."
“妖狐便能重获自己原本的力量”
"Having intercourse with its host is considered as a forbidden ritual,
“与宿主进行性交是一种禁忌仪式
"and the demon fox depends on the host..."
“妖股需要依靠宿主存活下去…”
This is bad. This is seriously bad!
糟了 这可不妙！
If you win against me, then I'll introduce you to Hayato.
如果你赢了我 那我就把你介绍给隼人
There.
中了
You got this.
你可以的
Izzy!
伊姬！
Wetty. What are you doing here?
汗仔 你来这做什么？
You weren't invited.
你没有受邀
What did you do that for?
你这是干什么？
Scram, you lowly nobody.
滚吧 你这无名鼠辈
Izzy, let's go.
伊姬 我们走
That...
那是…
Fucking bitch.
该死的贱人
Yeah!
耶！
We are currently at Hayato Ippongi's party!
我们目前正在 一本木隼人的派对上玩！
There you are!
你在这儿啊！
-Hikari! Where's Hachi? -What?
-小光！八公在哪里？ -什么？
Have you seen Hachi?
你有见到八公吗？
What? I can't hear you.
什么？我听不到你在说什么
-Hachi! -What?
-八公！ -诶？
Forget it!
算了！
There's something I want to say to you.
我有话想对你说
You're right. I'm taking it slowly.
你说得对 我很慢热
I'm not confident like Masato.
我不像正人那样自信
You do everything so abruptly, and that's completely different from me.
你的每个举动都是那么突然 和我的行事风格全然不同
So I don't know what to do.
所以我不知该如何是好
But...
但是…
I like you, too.
我也喜欢你
I think...
我觉得…
I mean, I want to have intercourse with you,
我是说 我想和你做爱
but what about afterwards?
但做完之后呢？
We support one another, right?
我们要彼此扶持 对吧？
That's having a cooperative relationship. That's partnership, right?
拥有一种合作关系 这才叫伴侣 不是吗？
A cooperative relationship...
合作关系…
Right, you and I will have a cooperative relationship,
你说得对 我们应该形成合作关系
and we will have intercourse, right now.
那我们做爱吧 现在就做
Yes.
好
We just made it in time.
我们刚好赶上最后的期限
What is this? This is no joke.
这是什么？太刺激了
You and I are now connected forever.
从现在开始 你和我永远绑定在一起了
Hayato!
隼人！
That's Ippongi's descendant.
那是一本木的后人
Let's get this party started!
派对正式开始！
Izzy?
伊姬？
-Cheers! -Cheers.
-干杯！ -干杯
Izzy.
伊姬
-There you are, Hachi! -What's up, buddy?
-找到你了 八公！ -你好吗 兄弟？
I know why she was so eager to have intercourse with you.
我知道她为什么急着跟你做爱了
For love, right?
是因为爱 对吧？
No! That girl is a demon fox,
不是！那姑娘是一只妖狐
and she has to have sex
她必须和召唤她的男人做爱
with the man who summoned her or she'll disappear.
否则她就会消失
It's a forbidden ritual involving spiritual powers
和那只妖怪做爱是一种
to have sex with that Yokai.
传递精气的禁忌仪式
When you have sex with her, you'll be connected to her
你和她做爱时 你们俩会产生连接
and she'll suck out your spiritual power.
而她会借此吸走你的精气
You'll be dependent on her powers,
之后你只能依赖她的妖力存活
and you won't be able to get away from her!
到时你就再也无法摆脱她了！
You haven't done it with her yet, right?
你还没和她做爱吧？
I just want to clarify this. How old are you?
我只想问清楚一点 你多大了？
You aren't underage, are you?
你不是未成年吧？
I'm 521 years old.
我521岁了
I don't get it,
我不懂你在说什么
but I'll take that as enthusiastic consent.
但我就当这是你热情似火的性同意了
What's this?
这是什么？
That's a charm for my family's prosperity.
这是令我的家族如此兴旺的符咒
Basically, it shows that I'm a super special person.
简单来说 它代表我是一个极其特别的人
Your ancestor was born in Yamato
你的祖先生于大和
and thrived as a carpenter.
是做木匠生意发家的
Isn't that right?
对不对？
How do you know that?
你怎么知道？
I've been looking for you.
我一直在找你
Hold on. Who are you?
等等 你是哪位？
Well...
这个嘛…
I'm the woman you longed for.
我是你渴望至极的女人
You are a Guardian, and my target.
你是守护者 也是我要杀死的对象
Izzy?
伊姬？
Izzy!
伊姬！
Have you seen Izzy? That girl who was with me?
你看到伊姬了吗？ 就是之前在我身边的那女孩
She left with Hayato.
她跟隼人走了
I bet they're having a good time in a private room right now!
我敢说他们正在某个私密房间 翻云覆雨呢！
INVESTIGATION DIVISION ONE
第一刑侦科
Yes. Thank you very much.
好 非常感谢
Is that Kouki Shikazono's laptop?
那是鹿苑科希的笔记本电脑吗？
Yes, I got it from his mother.
对 我问他母亲要来的
Dance at home.
要跳舞就回家跳
You got it.
知道了
Hi, everyone.
嗨 大家好
I found something incredible.
我找到了一个非常厉害的东西
A forbidden book
一本讲述了
with information about Yokai that was never revealed!
此前从不为人所知的妖怪的禁书！
What is to be revealed will affect the future of this world.
此书的内容一旦被公之于众 整个世界的未来都会受到影响
This forbidden book...
这本禁书...
Hello?
喂？
Yes, I'll be home late tonight. Can you put my dinner in the fridge?
好 今晚我要很晚才能回家 帮我把晚饭放冰箱 好吗？
Calm down me. I shouldn't rush this.
我得冷静一点 这件事不能着急
Now, everyone, listen carefully.
现在 请各位听好了
This is a story from ancient times.
这是一个发生在古时候的故事
Long time ago,
很久以前
humans and Yokai lived in perfect harmony.
人类与妖怪和睦地共存着
Humans and Yokai supported one another, and had a reciprocal relationship.
那时的人类与妖怪 相互扶持 互惠互利
He had intercourse with that...
他和那妖怪性交了…
What a foolish human.
真是个愚蠢之人
Izzy!
伊姬！
Izzy?
伊姬？
Perfect timing.
你来得正好
Is there a good place to store this?
有什么存放这玩意的好地方吗？